unify.com 2010-03-14

# Unify | Privacy Policy

Unify Corporation ("Unify", "We") respects the importance of protecting your personal information and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We recognize the need for appropriate protections and management of your personal information that you provide to us. Unify has therefore established this Privacy Statement to assist you to understand what information we collect and how that information is used. This Privacy Statement applies to Unify including its Divisions and its Subsidiary Companies.

## Safe Harbor Compliance

Unify’s privacy practices are in compliance with the U.S. and E.U. Safe Harbor principles. Information about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor certification can be found at [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor).

## What Personal Information Does Unify Corporation Collect?

Personal Information is information that can be used to identify or contact a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number or email address. Unify may collect certain personal information from customers, business partners, employees and candidates for employment. Unify does not collect personal information when you visit the Unify web sites unless you choose to provide such personal information.

On Unify web sites, you can order products or services, request information, subscribe to marketing or support materials, register to a secure extranet site to obtain access to product information and services, or apply for jobs at Unify. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs and passwords educational and employment background, job interest data and benefit choices.

## How Does Unify Corporation Use Personal Information?

Unify will use personal information to provide customers and business partners with information and services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to deliver products/services to you, to bill you for products/services you purchased, and to provide service and support. Occasionally we may use your information to contact you to complete surveys that we use for marketing and quality assurance purposes. Personal information collected online may be combined with information you provide to Unify through other sources such as trade shows or seminars.

Some of Unify’s websites make on-line newsgroups available to our users. Any information that is disclosed in these newsgroups becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Unify may, from time to time, send email regarding its products and services to users who have posted to our newsgroups. Each participant's opinion expressed in a newsgroup is his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of Unify.

To the extent that Unify uses personal information to email you about our product and services, Unify’s email practices are in compliance with the U.S. and E.U. SPAM laws.  Information about the U.S. and E.U. SPAM laws can be found at [http://www.spamlaws.com](http://www.spamlaws.com/).

Except as provided in this Statement, Unify does not use your personal information for a purpose other than the stated purpose for which such information is collected.

Personal information given to Unify may be transferred across state and country borders for data consolidation, storage and simplified information management.

## With Whom Does Unify Corporation Share Personal Information?

Unify may contract with third party service providers and suppliers to deliver marketing material, complete products, process online orders, and deliver services and customer solutions. Unify may share personal information with its service providers and suppliers for the sole purpose and only to the extent needed to support the customers' business needs. Service providers and suppliers are required to keep confidential the personal information received from Unify and may not use it for any purpose other than as originally intended.

We may also share your information with a distributor or partner in your area who can assist with your request for information if Unify does not have its own sales force in your area. The distributor or partner may use these details to contact you about the services that they may offer as well as other Unify products or services that you may be interested in. If you do not want to receive information from our distributors or partners, you may opt out by following the procedures set forth in the Choice/Opt-Out Section of this policy.

Third parties receiving personal information are expected to apply the same level of privacy protection as contained in this Privacy Statement.

Except as provided above, Unify will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by, or in connection with, law enforcement action, subpoena or other litigation, or applicable law.

Unify will not sell, trade or lease your personal information to others.

## Choice & Opt-Out

Unify does not require that you provide Unify with personal information. The decision to provide personal information is voluntary. If you do not wish to provide the personal information requested, however, you may not be able to proceed with the activity or receive the benefit for which the personal information is being requested.

If you would like to remove your information from our database or not receive future communications, or wish to change or modify information previously provided, please contact us at webmaster@unify.com. Upon receipt of your request, your information will be removed or updated within ten (10) business days of receipt of your request.

## Sensitive Information

Except as provided below, Unify does not request or receive sensitive information from visitors to our web sites. Unify may receive sensitive information such as medical or health conditions, or race and ethnic data regarding its employees in connection with the administration of its health and welfare benefit plans, or as part of government mandated recordkeeping requirements. Such information will not be shared with third parties without the employee's affirmative approval as required by applicable law. In addition, sensitive information will not be used for a purpose other than its original purpose without the employee's approval. Further, Unify will treat as sensitive any information received from a third party where the third party treats and identifies the information as sensitive.

## Access To and Accuracy of your Information

Unify strives to keep your personal information accurate. We have implemented technology, management processes and policies to maintain data accuracy. We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable effort to provide you with online access and the opportunity to change your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as a password and user ID, before granting access to your data.

Unify will not process personal information in a way that is incompatible with the purposes for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by the individual, as required by applicable law.

## Security of Personal Information

Unify is committed to taking reasonable efforts to secure the personal data you choose to provide us. To protect the privacy of any personal information you may have provided, Unify employs industry-standard controls including physical access controls, Internet firewalls, intrusion detection, and network monitoring. In addition, access to sensitive data as defined in this Statement is limited to those individuals and agents having a need to know.

## Other Information/Logging and Cookies

Unify collects and/or logs Internet Protocol addresses, Internet domain names, the web browser and operating system used to access the Unify web site, the files visited, the time spent in each file, and the time and date of each visit.

Unify also uses cookies on some of its web sites. Cookies are identifiers that can be sent from a web site via your browser to be placed on your computers’ hard drive. Thereafter when you visit a web site, a message is sent back to the web server by the browser accessing the web site. You may elect not to accept cookies by changing the designated settings on your web browser. However, not utilizing cookies may prevent you from using certain functions and features of web sites. The information collected from the use of cookies is used and analyzed to improve Unify’s web sites.

You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you and personalize your web-browsing experience.

## Links to Non-Unify Web Sites and Third Parties

The Unify web sites may provide links to third-party web sites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Unify web site. Unify does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from Unify’s. We do not endorse or make any representations about third party web sites. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is not covered by the Unify Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third party companies may choose to share their personal data with Unify; that sharing is governed by that third party company's privacy policy.

## Verification

Unify will engage in periodic self-assessment to verify that it continues to be in compliance with this Privacy Statement.

## Subscription Communications

Subscription communications include email newsletters, software updates, GLS, RSS feeds etc. that may be expressly requested by you or which you consented to receive. After you request such communications, you may opt out of receiving them by selecting the email "opt out" or "unsubscribe" link, or follow the opt-out instructions included in each subscription communication.

Please be aware that when you opt out of receiving certain subscription communications, it may affect the services you have chosen to receive from Unify where accepting the communications is a condition of receiving the services.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Statement or believe that the privacy of your personal information has not been respected, you may submit a complaint in writing to the attention of UNIFY HUMAN RESOURCES, 1420 Rocky Ridge Drive, Suite 380, Roseville, CA 95661.

## Dispute Resolution

If an employee living in an E.U. member country has a complaint regarding the transfer of human resources data to the U.S., Unify agrees to cooperate with the appropriate European data protection authority for handling such complaints. Unify agrees to handle all other disputes involving the transfer of personal data from the EU to the U.S. in accordance with the JAMS dispute resolution procedures.

Except as provided above, dispute resolution for all other individuals shall be in accordance with applicable law.

## Changes to this Statement

Unify will review and update this Statement periodically. Updated June 2009.
